<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>News on Blog Dude</title><link>https://blog/news/</link><description>Recent content in News on Blog Dude</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Copyright © 2023-2024 Albert Huynh. All Rights Reserved.</copyright><atom:link href="https://blog/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Kinda Sucks</title><link>https://blog/news/2024/01/markdown-kinda-sucks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 16:32:37 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog/news/2024/01/markdown-kinda-sucks/</guid><description><![CDATA[Image stolen from Adam Michael Wood
Basic font emphasis styles First of all, I think markdown is pretty good if you want to do basic stuff like italics, bold, strikeout, underli&ndash;. Oh what?? Markdown doesn&rsquo;t have a syntax for underline you say? Well what am I to do now. Oh maybe because markdown supports HTML5, I can use tags. What now? yOu cAN&rsquo;t dO thaT. This doesn&rsquo;t work either because this site can&rsquo;t do it for some inexplicable reason even though it&rsquo;s supposed to?]]></description><enclosure url="https://blog/news/2024/01/markdown-kinda-sucks/featured.png" length="688471" type="image/png"/></item><item><title>Name Change and Regenerating GPG Keys</title><link>https://blog/news/2024/01/name-change-and-regenerating-gpg-keys/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 14:51:34 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog/news/2024/01/name-change-and-regenerating-gpg-keys/</guid><description>https://www.tenor.co/view/this-is-fine-gif-5263684
I wonder how to give credit to the creator of this gif but the guy probably stole it from some other person, who stole it from some other person, and so on. Idk, you guys can check know your meme or something. Man this markdown thing is so janky. Why is it bold? I don&amp;rsquo;t want it to be bold. How the heck do I put a caption underneath this gif?</description><enclosure url="https://blog/news/2024/01/name-change-and-regenerating-gpg-keys/featured.gif" length="1925183" type="image/gif"/></item><item><title>Second Thoughts?</title><link>https://blog/news/2024/01/second-thoughts/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 20:20:08 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog/news/2024/01/second-thoughts/</guid><description><![CDATA[&quot;Mirror Pond [Explore]&quot; by mclcbooks is licensed under CC BY-NC-ND 2.0.
Would I be better off on a microblog site like Mastadon? This blog site is a bit more complicated than I thought. I mean some of you guys out there have probably made a website before, it&rsquo;s a bit&hellip;messy. Y&rsquo;all think it&rsquo;s easy to make all these sections? Bro, I spent the whole day figuring out how to properly make sections and nice little dropdown sidebar stuff for my docs.]]></description><enclosure url="https://blog/news/2024/01/second-thoughts/featured.png" length="1176614" type="image/png"/></item><item><title>First Post</title><link>https://blog/news/2024/01/first-post/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 16:50:23 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog/news/2024/01/first-post/</guid><description><![CDATA[Introduction This is my first post of my new blog website, Blog Dude (shoutout to whoever knows which game I&rsquo;m referring to). I couldn&rsquo;t have done it without the help of Razon Yang, the wonderful developer of the Hugo Bootstrap theme. He has helped me out a ton with this blog site (I&rsquo;ll be sure to clear the cache before I call you up). Well&hellip; I already took a week to figure out more git commands (I will never fully master all these confusing instructions), reading both Hugo docs and Razon&rsquo;s docs and trying to get GitHub pages to update my changes.]]></description><enclosure url="https://blog/news/2024/01/first-post/featured-sample.webp" length="498412" type="image/webp"/></item></channel></rss>