<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Networking on Blog Dude</title><link>https://blog/tags/networking/</link><description>Recent content in Networking on Blog Dude</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Copyright © 2023-2024 Albert Huynh. All Rights Reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 22:32:05 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog/tags/networking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I Bought a New Router</title><link>https://blog/docs/networking/openwrt/i-bought-a-new-router/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 22:32:05 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog/docs/networking/openwrt/i-bought-a-new-router/</guid><description>Intro Over the past week I have been looking at the project OpenWrt and checking out which routers to buy. How could I do this without consulting the home networking subreddit. Though, those people said I would need to spend like $400 or something buying ubiquiti unifi WAP, build a small pc for the router, build a pc for a firewall, etc. The task is daunting and even though I would love to do all of that.</description><enclosure url="https://blog/docs/networking/openwrt/i-bought-a-new-router/featured.png" length="220370" type="image/png"/></item><item><title>Docker Name Change</title><link>https://blog/docs/networking/docker/docker-name-change/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 17:06:25 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog/docs/networking/docker/docker-name-change/</guid><description>Updated Synology Version Over the past weekend I decided to update my Synology NAS server to a more up-to-date version. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t busy that day and fortunately, none of the users were online so that gave me more time in case something goes wrong. The network was back up and running but during that time frame, I was freaking out so much.
Docker Name Changes As I was rebooting the server and attempted to access my Docker containers, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find Docker located anywhere in my files.</description><enclosure url="https://blog/docs/networking/docker/docker-name-change/featured.png" length="35411" type="image/png"/></item><item><title>Updating to DSM 7.2.1</title><link>https://blog/docs/synology/updating-to-dsm-7.2.1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 17:05:32 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog/docs/synology/updating-to-dsm-7.2.1/</guid><description>Preface So as stated in my last post about the Docker name change, that issue arose from me updating my server to DSM 7.2. Would you believe it if I told you that wasn&amp;rsquo;t the only issue that I encountered? Along with that whole Docker name change, Synology Drive also messed up, and that included its dependencies like Synology Photos. I had to fix that ASAP as I had many users using those services.</description><enclosure url="https://blog/docs/synology/updating-to-dsm-7.2.1/featured.png" length="7591565" type="image/png"/></item></channel></rss>